
[
    {
      "question": "물",
      "answer": "Water"
    },
    {
      "question": "밥",
      "answer": "Rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "야채",
      "answer": "Vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "과일",
      "answer": "Fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "고기",
      "answer": "Meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "빵",
      "answer": "Bread"
    },
    {
      "question": "생선",
      "answer": "Fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "커피",
      "answer": "Coffee"
    },
    {
      "question": "맥주",
      "answer": "Beer"
    },
    {
      "question": "소주",
      "answer": "Soju"
    }
  ]
  